好了，接下来我会向大家示范如何通过三个简单的步骤
All right we're going to show you how to create a CursorLoader in three
创建一个CursorLoader
easy steps.
先创建一个整型的常量作为Loader ID
We start by creating an integer constant for a Loader ID.
然后实现Loader回调函数
Then we implement the Loader Call backs.
最后使用LoaderManager初始化Loader
Finally we initialize the Loader with the LoaderManager.
那我们就从创建Loader的ID开始，它是一个整型常量
We start just by creating a Loader ID, which is an integer constant.
一个activity可以使用不同的多个Loader
A single activity can use multiple Loaders and
它们是靠不同的ID来区分的
they are differentiated by these ID's.
然后我们需要把Loader的回调函数写完整
The we have to fill in the Loader Callbacks.
回调函数是一个接口类
The Loader Callbacks are a generic interface class,
带了一个参数化类型
with one parametrized type.
当我们通过CursorLoader使用回调函数的时候
When we use the Loader Callbacks with a CursorLoader, the parameterized type we
我们使用的这个参数化类型是Cursor
use is Cursor, which makes the callbacks look like they do here.
最有意思的事情是onCreateLoader
The most interesting one for us is onCreateLoader.
它返回了一个带有Cursor的loader
OnCreateLoader returns a loader with parameterized type, Cursor.
这是我们创建和返回CursorLoader的地方
This is where we create and return our CursorLoader.
CursorLoader有一个构造函数，带着所有标准的
CursorLoader has a constructor that takes all of the standard content
content provider的查询参数，并且按照我们的意愿调用content provider
provider query parameters, and will call the content provider on our behalf.
它是靠LoaderManager来执行的
When it is executed by the LoaderManager.
因为CursorLoader派生自Async TaskLoader
Since CursorLoader derives an Async TaskLoader,
它会在一个后台线程里执行
it will be executed in a background thread.
当它完成后 OnLoadFinished会执行，我们的数据也就绪了
OnLoadFinished is called when the loader completes, and our data is ready.
只需要调用SwapCursor就可以在cursor adaptor里使用数据了
To use the data in our cursor adaptor, we just call SwapCursor,
但是当数据就绪的时候 也是我们应该
but this is where we would also perform any other UI updates we'd want to make
去执行UI更新的地方
when the data is ready.
OnLoaderReset专门是在loader被销毁的时候调用的
OnLoaderReset is typically only called when our loader is being destroyed.
这意味着我们要移除所有Loader数据的引用
It means that we need to remove all references to the Loader Data.
为了做到这一点，我们调用cursorAdapter上的swapCursor方法，并传入null
To do that we call SwapCursor on our cursor adaptor with null.
最后，使用LoaderManager初始化我们的loader
Finally, we use the LoaderManager to initialize our loader.
我们传递一个ID
We pass in that loader ID,
刚才已经写好了的回调函数，还有一个可选的bundle
the loader call back we just filled out, and an optional bundle.
这就覆盖了所有loader的生命周期
This will do all that cool life cycle stuff we covered in the loader intro,
这样，如果loader还不存在，就调用onCreateLoader
such as, calling onCreate loader if the loader doesn't already exist.
当在fragment里使用loader的时候
When using loaders in a fragment,
我们在onActivityCreated方法里初始化loader
we initialize our loader in the onActivityCreated method.
这样你会得到一个基本的CursorLoader
And that's it, you've got a basic CursorLoader.
我们会在下一次练习时让你写一个
We're going to have you write one for our next exercise.